Morning.
So which one are you right now?
Aren't you...
Gojou Satoru.
I'm in charge of the
first-years at Jujutsu Tech.
Jujutsu...
Fushiguro... Senpai!
What is this?
I'm not sure you should
be worrying about others,
Itadori Yuuji.
It's been decided that you'll
be secretly executed.
Jujutsu Kaisen
Episode 1: Ryoumen Sukuna
Itadori
Hello, Sugisawa Hospital.
Oh, this is Itadori.
I just called earlier.
Yes.
I'm sorry to keep calling,
but how is my grandpa doing?
Huh? I thought they already told you.
Oh, please hold on.
I'll go ask myself.
Itadori-san never uses his call button.
It's actually scary that he doesn't.
Itadori-san, you have a phone call.
Yuuji-kun's asking if you
want him to bring any—
Leave me alone!
Tell him not to come!
He should go to his club! His club!
What? What's going on?
You heard him.
What club are you in, Yuuji-kun?
I heard.
I'll come by tomorrow evening.
Miyashiro Prefectural Sugisawa Third High School
They're keeping a cursed
object in a place like this?
Could they be any dumber?
There's nothing here.
Huh?
The Stevenson screen's empty.
For real? That's hilarious!
Maybe it took a nighttime stroll.
I'll punch you.
Well, no going home
until it's recovered, okay?
I'm seriously going to punch him next time.
Ready to go?
Are you really sure,
Occult Phenomenon
Research Club
Sasaki-senpai?
Iguchi-senpai?
Okay, here we go!
Spirits, spirits, please tell us...
Which creature is the council
president just barely weaker than?!
Ku
Ku-ri-o-ne (sea angel)?
ri
o
ne
Sea Angel
A type of plankton
living in cold oceans!
A transparent
body!
It's actually
related
to mollusks!
It moves its legs,
which look
like wings,
to float around.
When capturing prey,
its mouth pops open
and shoots out tentacles!
Eek!
A sea angel can beat him?!
What a small fry!
Occult club!
Hey, Plankton President! What's up?
Notice
As you were previously informed,
a research club with no real activities
must forfeit its club room.
So vacate this room at once!
You shouldn't underestimate
our members, President.
Mysterious Events
File 9
What is that?
You know about our rugby field
being closed off, right?
Yes.
Some of the students who fell
ill were actually hospitalized.
Don't you think that's strange?
We're talking about tough rugby players here.
Truth is, the players said
they started hearing
mysterious sounds and voices
right before they fell ill.
That's when we found this newspaper
article from thirty years ago.
Belongings Found
on Roadside,
Possible Crime
It talks about the disappearance of Yoshida-san,
who worked with the construction company,
Former Employee, Age 35, Goes Missing at Sugisawa
Former Employee of a
Major Construction Company
Never Made a Comeback
and Went Into Debt
Last
Sighted
at
Sugisawa
Third
Laid Off from Work
Failed to Start New Enterprise
Possible Suicide
and it mentions he was last sighted here at
Sugisawa Third High School during construction.
Laid Off from Work
Failed to Start New Enterprise
Yoshida-san was struggling to make ends meet,
Continuous Collection Calls
Threatening Calls and Faxes
so he turned to loan sharks
and those organizations were after him.
Suspicious Men at His Home
Possible Kidnapping
Which means!
The whole disaster at the
rugby field was caused by
the vengeful spirit of Yoshida-san,
who's buried there!
Vengeful Spirit
No, it was caused by ticks.
Hard Ticks
A large,
parasitic tick
that sucks the blood
of animals and humans!
Be careful, because they can be carriers of
infectious diseases that lead to death if they bite humans!
Diseases such as Severe Fever with Thrombocytopenia Syndrome (SFTS)
Hmm?
They leap onto targets
from grass and bushes.
Burp
Leap
Size
Before Blood
After Blood
After sucking blood, their size
can increase up to 100x!
Hard ticks.
A large, blood-sucking bug.
If one bites you and infects you with SFTS,
it can be fatal, so be very careful.
So what?!
The occult club is trying
to uncover occult activity,
so it's still a proper club activity report!
This isn't some kid's game!
Besides, the biggest problem is you,
Itadori Yuuji!
You're registered with track
and field, not the occult club,
so this club doesn't even have the
three members required for any club!
Not Enough Members
Huh?
Itadori...
No, I know I wrote down the occult club.
I rewrote it!
The track and field coach, Takagi!
Itadori, we need you so we
can conquer the nationals!
A teacher more problematic than
the students just showed up...
Give it a rest! How many times
do I have to tell you I refuse?
You can't!
Why can't I?!
However, I'm not some demon!
If you can beat me, then I'll give up on you.
Let's settle it fair and square on the track!
Now it's interesting!
You're on!
Track and Field Coach
Takagi
Itadori
Is it "fair and square" to rewrite
a student's club application?
What's with this rugby field?
Is there a dead body
buried here or something?
Even if there is,
I'm surprised to see one this high-leveled.
That's probably a grade 2 curse.
Must be that cursed object's influence.
No Unauthorized Entry
Damn it.
Its presence is too strong to pin down.
It feels like it's close by,
but it could still be far away, too.
This special-grade cursed
object is a serious pain.
Who could have moved it?
Where is it now?
Over here!
Coach Takagi is taking on
Itadori from West Middle!
Wow, what are they competing in?
Yeah!
Fourteen meters!
*Japan's National Record
Wow, Takagi's still got it!
Itadori! Itadori!
What're you gonna do, Itadori?!
Hey, is Itadori famous or something?
They're probably tall tales, but I heard
he beat all stages of Ninja Warrior,
and that he's the reincarnation
of Mirko Cro Cop.
But Mirko's not even dead yet.
Still, he earned the nickname
"Tiger of West Middle."
Lame.
Hey, can I just throw this however I want?
Yep. I won't call any fouls,
so throw however you please.
Sorry.
I wanted to demonstrate how
serious I am by intentionally
choosing something that isn't your forte—
Uh, roughly thirty meters.
*World Record
Yeah, I win!
He's more gorilla than tiger, isn't he?
That was a pitcher's throw.
Itadori, you'd do well on a sports team.
You don't have to force yourself to
stay in our occult club, y'know.
Huh?
But as much as you two love scary things,
you couldn't go to haunted
places without me, could you?
Shiver
Tremble
3 Days Ago
We're scared because we like it.
Yay!
Besides, this school requires
everyone to be in a club, right?
I couldn't keep up with this.
You don't have to do anything!
You can be a ghost member!
Occult Phenomenon
Research Club
We're the occult club, after all!
I did say that.
I want to be able to go home
by 5 PM for my own reasons.
So if it's okay with you, I'd like to stay.
I like the atmosphere of
the occult club a lot.
Well, if that's how it is, we don't mind.
Yeah.
That guy's incredible.
He pulled that off without any cursed energy.
I wonder if he's like Zenin-senpai...
Oh, it's already half past four!
Well, Coach, I've got stuff to do! Later!
The presence of a cursed object!
Hey, you!
He's way too fast!
I heard he can run fifty
meters in three seconds.
Is he a car?
*World Record
5.47s+
Just listen well.
There's something I want
to tell you before the end.
It's about your parents.
I said I'm not interested.
Grandpa, could stop trying to
act all cool before you die?
Every man wants to go out in style, you know!
Get a clue, you useless grandson!
Quit snapping over everything.
You can just be yourself.
Tsk. Lax upbringing.
Yuuji.
Hmm?
You're a strong kid, so help others.
Even if it's only those closest to you,
just save the people you can.
It's okay if you lose your way,
and don't worry about whether
they'll thank you or not.
Just save as many people as you can,
even if it's only one.
When you die, you should
be surrounded by people.
Don't end up like me.